https://www.tfaw.com/privacy-policy/

*PLEASE NOTE: COVID-19 measures may cause processing and shipping delays. Learn More *
Privacy Policy
Please keep in mind that if you're using this site, you are agreeing to the Privacy Policy of Things From Another World, Inc. (TFAW.com).
This Privacy Notice describes the types of personal information we collect about our customers on our Website, in our stores, and through interest-based online advertising. The Privacy Notice also describes how we may use that information, how we protect that information, how we share that information, your choices and options regarding the information, and how you can contact us regarding our privacy practices.
Information we Collect
We may collect certain personal information from you in connection with your activities at TFAW.com, such as when you shop on our website or in our stores. This information may include:
Payment card or other financial account information;contact and billing information (including name, e-mail address, postal address, and phone number);date of birth;geolocation data; andother personal information you provide to us on our Website, in our stores, or when you interact with us in other ways, both online and offline.Additionally, we or companies acting on our behalf may collect certain computer and browser information through automated technologies such as cookies and web beacons when you visit our Website. A "cookie" is a file that a website sends to a visitor's computer or other Internet-connected device to identify the browser or to store information or settings in the browser. A "web beacon," also known as an Internet tag, pixel tag or clear GIF, links web pages to web servers and their cookies and may be used to transmit information collected through cookies back to a web server.
The information collected using these tools may include your IP address, browser characteristics, operating system, the address of the web page that referred you to our Website, dates and times of Website visits, the language your system uses, and the country and time zone in which your device is located. These automated technologies also permit the collection of "clickstream data," which may include a log of content you access while browsing a website.
Companies acting on our behalf may combine the information collected from your visit to our Website with other information they have collected previously. Your web browser may tell you how to be notified when you receive certain types of cookies and how to restrict, reject or disable certain cookies.
Interest-Based online Advertising and Google Analytics
This section of our Privacy Notice provides details about interest-based online advertising (also called "targeted advertising", "remarketing", or "behavioral advertising"), Google Analytics, and your choices with respect to this type of advertising.
We use Google Analytics' 3rd-party audience data such as age, gender and interests to better understanding the behavior of our customers and work with companies that collect information about your online activities to provide advertising targeted to suit your interests and preferences. For example, you may see certain ads on other websites because we contract with Google and other similar companies to target our ads based on information we or they have collected, including information that was collected through automated means (such as cookies and web beacons). These companies also use automated technologies to collect information when you click on our ads, which helps track and manage the effectiveness of our marketing efforts.
You may opt out of the automated collection of information by third-party ad networks for the purpose of delivering advertisements tailored to your interests, by visiting the consumer opt-out page for the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising here and edit or opt-out your Google Display Network ads preferences at https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated. Because those opt-out and preference control pages are specific to the individual browser used to visit it, and because those pages are not operated by TFAW.com, we are unable to perform the opt-outs on your behalf.
How we Use the Personal Information we Collect
When we collect information from you, we may use it for a number of purposes, including to:
Process, manage, complete and account for transactions, including purchases and refunds;
Provide our products and services to you and fulfill your gift card orders;
Identify your product and service preferences;
Improve merchandise selections and customer service;
Invite you to participate in customer research;
Notify you about new products, services, features, promotions, events and special offerings relating to TFAW.com we think you will find
valuable;
Provide customer support and respond to your requests, comments and inquiries;
Create and manage online accounts you establish;
Administer your participation in promotions, contests and sweepstakes;
Verify your identity in certain instances (such as when you return merchandise or request a refund);
Protect against, identify and help prevent fraud, unauthorized activity, claims and other liabilities and minimize credit risk;
Comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, industry standards, our policies, and our Terms of Use; and performing market
research, and administering our Website.
We also may use the information in other ways for which we provide specific notice at the time of collection.
We also may use the information in other ways for which we provide specific notice at the time of collection.
In addition, we use information collected online through automated means for purposes such as customizing our users' visits to TFAW.com, delivering content tailored to our users' interests and the manner in which our users browse our Website, measuring and managing the advertising effectiveness of our online and offline advertisements and events, and managing our business. We also use this information to help diagnose technical and service problems, administer our Website, identify users of our Website, and gather demographic information about our users. We use clickstream data to determine how much time users spend on web pages of our websites, how users navigate through our websites, and how we may tailor our websites to better meet the needs of our users. In order for us to maintain the accuracy of your personal information and improve our communication with you, we may also supplement the information we collect with other public demographic information.
Links/Co-Branded Sites
TFAW.com has established relationships with advertisers and reputable business partners that allow visitors to our Site to link directly to sites operated by these partners. Some of these sites may be "co-branded" with a TFAW.com logo; however, they are not operated or maintained by TFAW.com. These sites may collect personal information from you. This Privacy Policy will apply to any personal information we obtain in this manner from our partners.
TFAW.com chooses its advertisers and business partners carefully. However, TFAW.com is not responsible for the content or practices of Web sites operated by third parties that are linked to our Site. These links are meant for the user's convenience only. Links to third-party sites do not constitute sponsorship, endorsement, or approval by TFAW.com of the content, policies, or practices of such third-party sites. We are not responsible for any information these sites may obtain and do not oversee their policies or practices in collecting personal information. Therefore, once you have left this Site via such a link, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third-party site.
This Site may also be linked to Web sites operated by companies affiliated with TFAW.com. TFAW.com may share information collected by our affiliated companies, however this Privacy Policy will apply to any personal information we receive in this manner. Visitors to our affiliated company's sites should still refer to their separate privacy policies and practices when providing any personally identifiable information.
Reviewing and Making Changes to Personally Identifiable Information
Visitors may review, change, or delete personal information from our records at any time. If you would like to review, change, or delete your personal information, please contact us at "privacy1 at tfaw dot com" or write us at Things From Another World, Attn: Privacy Info, 10956 SE Main St, Milwaukie, OR 97222. If you have requested the deletion of your information, we will immediately delete your information from our database and refrain from collecting any other personally identifiable information. However, there may be residual information that will remain within our databases that may or may not contain personally identifiable information for purposes of identifying purchases made through our Website. This residual information will not be given to any other third-party or used for any commercial purpose.
Security and Integrity of Personal Information
TFAW.com has established and maintains reasonable procedures to protect the confidentiality, security, and integrity of personal information collected by this Site, in compliance with PCI DSS requirements.
Collection and use os Personally Identifiable Information from Children Under 13
We do not seek nor will we knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 13.
Privacy Policy Changes
TFAW.com reviews its privacy policy periodically, and it may be subject to change.
Last Updated March 14th, 2018
Privacy Policy
Terms & Conditions
Affiliate Program
Gift Certificates
Contact Us
Help
Cookie Notice
This website uses cookies so you can place orders and we can provide the most secure and effective website possible. By using tfaw.com you accept our use of cookies.
Accept
Close
Privacy Policy
Cookie Settings
